Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 43: Williamsburg, circa 1985 - circa 2010
  - Bamonte's Restaurant, 32 Withers Street (between Lorimer Street and Union Avenue), Williamsburg, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - EXT View of Manhattan, Giando on the water, Williamsburg, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Store (Artist's Studio), 100 South 6th Street at Bedford Avenue, Williamsburg, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - INT/EXT Johnny's Apartment, 84 Berry Street Apt. 2L between North 8th and North 9th Street, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Grocery [Bayamon Grocery Store], 427 Wythe, Williamsburg, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Store (Apartment), 45 Broadway at Wythe Avenue, Williamsburg, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Williamsburg - Neighborhoods/Houses, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - EXT Vacant lot, Kent Avenue and Division Avenue, Williamsburg, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - INT/EXT Irish pub: Teddy's Bar and Grill, 96 Berry Street at North 8th Street, Williamsburg, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - INT Bar, Teddy's Bar and Grill, 96 Berry Street at North 8th Street, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - EXT School and lot, John D. Wells JHS 50, South 3rd Street (between Driggs Avenue and Roebling Street), 1996 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - INT Sheriff's Hallway, 97 South 2nd Street (between Berry Street and Wythe Avenue), Williamsburg, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - INT/EXT Omar's Ironworks, Flame Cut Steel Products Company, Inc., 242-246 Bedford Avenue (at North 5th Street), Williamsburg, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    This location was scouted for OK Garage. This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Warehouses."
  - INT/EXT Bistro Des Artistes, 115 Grand Street (between Wythe Avenue and Berry Street), 1996 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - INT Bar, Teddy's Bar and Grill, Berry Street and corner of North 8th Street, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - EXT Johnny's building/street, 106 North 8th Street (off Kent Avenue), 1996 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - INT/EXT Rachel's school/lot, Brooklyn High School of Automotive Trades, Bedford Avenue between North 12th Street and Nassau Ave (McCarren Park), 1996 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - INT Bar, Uncle Tony's Place, Driggs Avenue (between North 7th Street and North 8th Street), 1996 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - 150 North 9th Street, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - INT/EXT Johnny's Building, 140 North 8th Street, between Bedford Avenue and Berry Street, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - INT Sheriff's Hallway, 106 North 8th Street (between Berry Street and Wythe Avenue), Williamsburg, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - INT Bar, Northside Bar and Grill, 119 Kent Avenue at North 9th Street, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT School/lot, P.S. 196, Bushwick Avenue and Meserole Street, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT School/lot, JHS 126 John Ericsson, 424 Leonard Street at Bayard Street, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - INT Classroom, Sts. Peter and Paul School, 288 Berry Street (between South 2nd Street and South 3rd Street), 1996 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT Rachel's school/lot, Harry van Arsdale High School, 257 North 6th Street at Roebling Street, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT Mugs Ale House, 125 Bedford Avenue at North 10th Street, Williamsburg, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Williamsburg, Grand Avenue and Hooper Street, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Williamsburg, Fillmore Place (between Driggs Avenue and Roebling Street), 1997 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, Bedford Avenue (corner of North 11th Street), 1997 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - INT/EXT Sheriff's Apartment, 79 South 6th Street, 3rd floor, Williamsburg, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 129 Bedford Avenue (between North 9th Street and North 10th Street), Williamsburg, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - EXT/INT Bar and grill, Northside Café, 119 Kent Avenue, Williamsburg, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 792 Metropolitan Avenue at Bushwick Avenue, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - INT Hearing room, Williamsburg Art and Historical Center, 135 Broadway at Bedford Avenue, Williamsburg, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - EXT/INT Diner, T and S Diner, 206 Kent Street (at Metropolitan Avenue), Williamsburg, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - EXT/INT Tavern, Café Right Bank, Broadway at Kent Street, Williamsburg, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - EXT/INT Diner, Sabrina's Place, Broadway and Berry Street, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Williamsburg, Grand Street (between Wythe Avenue and Berry Street), 1997 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - EXT Neighborhood Bar, under Williamsburg Bridge, Wythe Avenue and South 5th Street, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood bar/Restaurant, On the Rocks, Kent Street at South 5th Street, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - INT Apartment, 2nd Floor, 333 Berry Street (South 5th Street and South 4th Street), Williamsburg, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Tavern, Teddy's Bar and Grill, 96 Berry Street at North 8th Street, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - INT Restaurant, Wet Paint Restaurant, 124 North 6th Street at Berry Street, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - 470 Flushing Avenue, 2nd Floor, Williamsburg, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - INT Loft, 60 Broadway (between Berry Street and Wythe Avenue), Williamsburg, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Loft, 60 Broadway between Berry Street and Wythe Avenue, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Roberto Clemente Ballfield, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Holding area, Royal Wine Company, north parking lot of 420 Kent Avenue, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT Junky's loft, 241 Bedford Avenue at North 3rd Street, circa 2000 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Industrial Street, Metropolitan Avenue at Stewart Avenue, Williamsburg, circa 2000 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Williamsburg Bridge, 47 South 5th Street (Kent Avenue and Wythe Avenue), circa 2000 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 100 Berry Street Apt. 1L, circa 2000 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Store / Apartment: 229 Bedford Avenue at North 4th Street, Williamsburg, circa 2000 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - INT Loft, 70 Grand Street, circa 2000 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Giando, 400 Kent Avenue at Broadway, Williamsburg, circa 2000 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Williamsburg Bridge, circa 2000 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - 245 Varet Street (between Bogart Street and White Street), 2nd Floor, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - INT Restaurant, Giando on the Water, 400 Kent Avenue, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Storefronts, Broadway at Hooper Street and Division Avenue, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - South 6th Street (off Bedford Avenue) and Williamsburg Bridge, Williamsburg, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - The Pod, 141 North 7th Street, Williamsburg, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Grand Ferry Park, Grand Street and Kent Avenue, Williamsburg, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - EXT Police Precinct, 37 Herbert Street at Humboldt Street, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - 150 South 1st Street, Corner of Bedford Avenue, Apt. 4K, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - 36-46 South 4th Street between Kent Street and Wythe Avenue, Apt. D7, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - The Abbey, 536 Driggs Avenue between North 7th Street and North 8th Street, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Studio, 37 South 3rd Street between Kent Avenue and Wythe Avenue, Apt. 1N, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Warehouse, 481 Wythe Avenue between South 10th Street + 11th Street, Williamsburg, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Grand Press, 284 Grand Street between Roebling Street and Havemeyer Street, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment building, 728 Driggs Avenue, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - INT/EXT Bar Restaurant, Frost Italian Restaurant, 193 Frost Street at Humboldt Street, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - EXT Park, Grand Ferry Park, Grand Street at Kent Avenue/River Street, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - North Side Bank, 33 Grand Street (between Kent Avenue and Wythe Avenue), 2004 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Williamsburg Art and Historical Center, 135 Broadway at Bedford Avenue, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 330 Wythe Avenue (between South 1st Street and South 2nd Street), Williamsburg, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - 413 Kent Avenue (between South 8th Street and Broadway), 2004 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - INT Mika's Apartment, 132 North 5th Street Apt. 3F (between Bedford Avenue and Berry Street), Williamsburg, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - EXT/INT Diner, 82 Broadway at Berry Street, Williamsburg, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Italian Restaurant, Bamonte's Restaurant, 32 Withers Street, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - EXT/INT Recording Studio, Mission Sound Recording, 16 Powers Street (between Rodney Street and Keap Street), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT School, Boricua College, 186 North 6th Street, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Giando on the Water, 400 Kent Avenue, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Russian Orthodox Cathedral, 228 North 12th Street at Driggs Avenue, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - INT/EXT Artist's Loft, 160 Berry Street between North 5th Street and North 4th Street, Williamsburg, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - INT/EXT Junky's loft, 85 North 3rd Street, 4th Floor, Williamsburg, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - 908 Kent Avenue, Williamsburg, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - 35 Broadway between Wythe Avenue and Kent Avenue, circa 2005 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - EXT Diner, empty diner, Wythe Avenue and North 3rd Street, Williamsburg, circa 2005 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - [South 6th Street and Berry Street, Williamsburg], circa 2005 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - INT Apartment, 72 North 8th Street, Apt. 2, Williamsburg, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - EXT Brian's Stoop, 176 North 6th Street (between Driggs Avenue and Bedford Avenue), 2005 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    This location was scouted for Love Monkey.
  - Richie's Loft Apartment, 338 Berry Street at South 5th Street, 7th floor, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - EXT / INT Brooklyn Loft, 245 Kent Avenue at Grand Street, 2nd Floor, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - INT Storefront/Loft, 143 Roebling Street, 2nd Floor Loft, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - INT Loft Apartment, 100 Metropolitan Avenue, APT 2A, at Wythe Avenue, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - 324 Ten Eyck Street (between Waterbury Street and Bogart Street), 2006 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - INT Loft Apartment, 119 Kent Avenue at North 7th Street, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - EXT / INT Brooklyn Loft, 33 Grand Street at Kent Avenue, Ground Floor, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - INT (raw) Loft, above Galapagos, 70 North 6th Street (between Kent Avenue and Wythe Avenue), 2006 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - INT Loft Apartment, 93 North 1st Street (at Wythe Avenue), 2006 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - INT Loft Apartment, 79-83 Metropolitan Avenue, 85 Metropolitan Avenue, 87 Metropolitan Avenue (between Wythe Avenue and Kent Avenue), 2006 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Richie's Loft, 83 North 1st Street (between Wythe Avenue and Berry Street), 2006 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - North 12th Street at Bedford Avenue, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Office, 390 Kent Avenue (near Broadway), NYC Shops/Facilities and Construction, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - EXT Streets, Broadway at Leonard Street, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - INT Loft Apartment, 100 Metropolitan Avenue, Apt. 2B (at Wythe Avenue), 2006 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - EXT/INT Auto shop, Joe's Auto Repair Corner, Inc., 445 Metropolitan Avenue at North 6th Street and Meeker Street, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - EXT Houses/Street (No Trees), Berry Street (between North 8th Street and North 9th Street), Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - EXT Streets, Broadway at Lorimer Street, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Loft, 285 Kent Avenue at South 2nd Street, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - South 6th Street and Broadway, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Scrap Metal Shop - Williamsburg, G and G Scrap Metal, 51 South 4th Street between Kent Street and Wythe Avenue, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT Cleaners/Tailors, Manuel Baez, 358 Broadway, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - McCarren Park, Bedford Avenue at North 12th Street, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - INT "Burger King," Dokebi Bar and Grill, 199 Grand Street between Driggs Avenue and Bedford Avenue, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - South 6th Street and Broadway, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - EXT / INT Brooklyn Loft, 35 Broadway at Dunham Place, 2nd Floor, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - INT Storefront, 96 North 6th Street, 2nd Floor, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - EXT Playground, William Sheridan Playground, Grand Street at Wythe Avenue, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Domino Lot, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - INT Storefront, 134 Kingsland Avenue at Beadel Street, Williamsburg, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Fillmore Place between Driggs Avenue and Roebling Street, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Catholic School / Church / Convent / Rectory, St. Cecilia's, 84 Herbert Street, between North Henry Street and Monitor Street, circa 2007 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - INT Apartment, 47 Grand Street, 1st Floor (between Kent Avenue and Wythe Avenue), 2007 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - EXT Church, St. Paul's Lutheran Church, 334 South 5th Street at Rodney Street, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - EXT Devoe Street Baptist Church, 140 Devoe Street (between Manhattan Avenue and Graham Avenue), 2007 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - EXT Church, St. Paul's Lutheran Church, Rodney Street and South 5th Street, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT Seedy Rock Club / Bar, Trash Bar, 256 Grand Street at Roebling Street, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - EXT Training Room, 17 South 6th Street at Kent Avenue, Williamsburg, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - EXT Impound Lot, Department of Citywide Administrative Services, 390 Kent Avenue between Broadway and South 6th Street, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - EXT Manhattan Reveal, Manhattan Bridge from pedestrian walkway, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment, 149-151 Grand Street, Williamsburg, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment building, 97 North 1st Street, Williamsburg, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment, 96 North 8th Street, Williamsburg, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment, 65 North 8th Street, Williamsburg, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment building, 93 South 2nd Street, Williamsburg, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - I/E Irish Pub, Zabloski's, 107 North 6th Street (between Wythe Avenue and Berry Street), 2009 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - EXT Biker Bar/Diner, Relish, Williamsburg, 225 Wythe Avenue, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Vacant Building, Williamsburg, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - EXT Opening Sequence, South 6th street, Berry Street, South 4th Street, Williamsburg, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Society of Saint Cono, 231-233 Ainslie Street between Manhattan Avenue and Graham Avenue, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Vacant office, Williamsburg [240 Kent Avenue, Kent Avenue and North 1st Street], 2009 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - EXT Walk and Talk, Bedford Avenue between Metropolitan Avenue and North 8th Street, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - EXT Brooklyn block, Havemeyer Street between Metropolitan Avenue and Grand Street, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - EXT Aaron Black - Machine Man, 330 Wythe Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Domino Sugar Factory Lot, Williamsburg, circa 2010 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - EXT Aaron Black - Machine Man, 475 Kent Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Series 44: Multiple neighborhoods, circa 1990 - 2007
  Series 44: Multiple neighborhoods includes location scout dossiers with photographs that span multiple Brooklyn neighborhoods: Flatbush, Brooklyn Heights, Mapleton, Sunset Park, Gravesend, Bath Beach, Plumb Beach, Gowanus, Red Hook, Vinegar Hill, Brooklyn Navy Yard, Fort Greene, Bushwick, Ocean Hill, Cobble Hill, Carroll Gardens, Boerum Hill, Brighton Beach, Coney Island, Williamsburg.
  The Scope and Contents note under each folder title provides further information about the content.
  - Manhattan exteriors (assorted), movie theaters, circa 1990 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    This folder includes photographs of 925 Flatbush Avenue / Astor Theatre, RKO Century, 102 Court Street / Cinart Cinema, 6401 18th Avenue / Walker Theater, 5205 4th Avenue / Coliseum Theatre, 1027 Flatbush Avenue / Kings Theatre.
  - INT Subway B, D, Q, M Lines, Bay 50th Street to 47-50th Streets, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Various dance studios, circa 1995 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    This folder includes photographs of New School of Dance, The New York Dance and Fitness Center, Inc., Miss Doreen's Reflections in Dance (1644 Bath Avenue), Miss M's Dance Center (5th Avenue).
  - EXT Highway, Belt Parkway, circa 1995 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    This folder includes photographs of Exit 4 (14th Avenue and Bay 8th Street), Exit 9B (Knapp Street), Exit 11N (Flatbush Avenue), and the Plumb Beach rest area.
  - EXT Streets, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    This folder includes photographs of under the Brooklyn-Queens Expressway, Hamilton Avenue at Centre Street, under the F line at Smith Street and 9th Street, Lorraine Street and Smith Street, 17th Street and Hamilton Avenue, Smith Street and Nelson Street, 3rd Avenue at 25th Street. Also includes photographs of locations in Queens: 54th Avenue at 46th Street, 54th Avenue at 44th Street, under the Brooklyn-Queens Expressway on Laurel Hill Boulevard, 54th Road and 44th Street.
  - EXT Streets, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    This folder includes photographs of Sands Street and Jay Street, Plymouth Street between Gold Street and Hudson Avenue, Flushing Avenue between Adelphi Street and Carlton Avenue, Flushing Avenue and Clermont Avenue, GMD Shipyard Corporation at Brooklyn Navy Yard.
  - EXT Streets, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    This folder includes photographs of Broadway, Wythe Avenue, Myrtle Avenue and Lewis Avenue, Stockton Street (between Lewis Avenue and Broadway), Broadway and Stewart Street, Broadway, Fulton Street and Atlantic Avenue, Broadway and Somers Street, Fulton Street and Van Sinderen Avenue.
  - Cobble Hill, Carroll Gardens, Boerum Hill Neighborhoods, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    This folder includes photographs of President Street, Nelson Street and Dennett Place, St. Mary's Playground, Luquer Street and Smith Street, Hoyt Street and Sackett Street, Hoyt Street and Bergen Street, Brooklyn Inn, Cobble Hill Pet Shoppe, Tuk Tuk, Salon de Quartier, Smith Street and Degraw Street, Roux Roux, Balluchi's, Cafe Luluc, and Artscetera.
  - EXT Brighton Beach Boardwalk and Coney Island Boardwalk, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous streets, Translight possibilities, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    This folder contains photographs of Columbia Street, Carroll Street and Henry Street in Carroll Gardens, Berry Street at North 9th Street in Williamsburg, Hoyt Street at Degraw Street in Carroll Gardens, Amity Street at Court Street in Cobble Hill, Smith Street at Sackett Street and Degraw Street in Cobble Hill, and Carmine Street and Bleecker Street in Manhattan.